8th Floor
Huh?
Arai... just now... you were
going downstairs. right?
Kobeni. make a double
peace sign and stay put.
Well. shit.
Aki... what's going on here?
It has to be a devil's power at work.
Kobeni. stand right there.
Why are there rooms
on the other side of the window?
Hey! None of the windows go anywhere!
They just open to the room across the hall!
I figured as much.
We're trapped on the eighth floor.
8th Floor
Let's run through what we know.
This is probably a devil's doing.
and no matter how many times
we try to go to a different floor.
we end up on the eighth again.
The elevator is inoperable
for whatever reason.
There's no way outside via
the rooms or any windows.
We tried going through the ceiling.
but ended up on the eighth floor again.
Maybe it's because Power killed that devil?
He coulda died while using
the power to keep us trapped.
And now—
You commanded me to kill him!
Did not!
A devil's powers are released
when they die. It can't be that.
Is the flesh piece reacting. Aki?
Actually...
It's gone dead still.
That devil before was bait. and we bit hard.
I've never seen a devil try
something so clever before.
But if no one hears from us for a while.
won't other Devil Hunters
show up to help?
I guess we better hope they don't fall
into the same kind of trap. then.
We're all gonna die here.
We're gonna starve to death.
H-Hang in there. Kobeni!
Didn't you become a Devil Hunter
to send your brother to college?!
They basically forced me to do it.
My parents are set on my
older brother going to college.
since he's the gifted one.
So they made me get a job.
It was become a Devil Hunter
or a sex worker!
I wanted to go to college. too!
And now I'm gonna die here!
Her face...!
Enough!
Quit laughing!
Kobeni. devils love fear. okay?
If you get scared. you're giving them
what they want. sweetie.
But I'm so scared!
Something bothering you. too. Aki?
The clocks in this room...
have been stuck at 8:18 for a while now.
In every single room... it's 8:18.
There's a chance that time has been
frozen here on the eighth floor.
And if that's the case. no one is coming.
Oh. shit! Then we can sleep all we want. right?
How stupid are you?
We might be trapped in here forever.
I mean. we might be. but we
might not be. too. y'know?
Wake me when you figure it out.
This bed is freaking sweet.
It'd be stupid not to sleep in it.
I owe the devil for this nap.
He's actually asleep...
Denji.
Rise and shine. Denji.
We find a way off the eighth floor yet?
Hate to break it to you. but not yet.
We found out the water and electricity
are still working while you were asleep.
There was a little bit of food that some of
the guests who ran must've left behind.
I'll be honest. everyone's really worn out.
Aki's been searching
for the devil nonstop.
I told him to take a break.
but he won't listen.
Arai was helping Aki at first.
but now he's locked himself up in
another room to have a panic attack.
Kobeni freaked out and tried to drink
toilet bowl water. so I knocked her out.
And as for the Fiend...
Something happen to Power?
Given there's nothing else to do.
I've decided to win the Nobel Prize!
Once I've earned such glorious esteem.
the humans will all kowtow to me!
And with the Nobel Prize as my foothold.
I shall ascend to the prime minister's throne!
What better way to ensure human suffering?
My first act will be passing a 100% sales tax!
She's always like that.
Huh. Okay. then.
Let's take turns watching Kobeni and Arai.
I couldn't even use the bathroom
when it was just me.
Well. this is my last cigarette.
I'm bored by how little this upsets you.
I can take it easy because
Aki's working hard.
The nicotine also helps!
Gotta have a port in a storm. right?
Life is sweeter with a bit of dependence.
Hey. that's the same brand he smokes.
That's because Aki learned all
about the flavor of cigarettes
from yours truly!
Not gonna smoke. Aki?
No. It's bad for your bones.
You should start. It's great for socializing.
I'm not looking to make friends.
Let me guess why you joined Public Safety.
You're out to kill the Gun Devil. right?
Everyone who signs up with a chip
on their shoulder is the same...
since only Public Safety is allowed to hold
onto pieces of the Gun Devil's flesh.
Devil Hunters die young anyway.
Might as well smoke.
I don't plan on dying any time soon.
I'll hold you to that.
It's a pain in the ass
when your partner dies.
What the hell was that?
She was my old partner's girlfriend.
It happens a lot. You get issues with the
family and friends of dead partners.
They can't do anything to get back
at the devils. so they take it out on me.
I just consider it something
that comes with the territory.
What was that about?
I put gum on the clothes
of that girl who hit you.
You shouldn't just sit back
and take being treated like that.
No need for you to feel guilty.
I was pissed off.
So I got some payback.
Serves her right.
She's gonna waltz around without realizing
there's a wad of gum on her clothing.
There's something my master said...
Devils don't fear Devil Hunters
who are strong or brave.
They fear Devil Hunters who have a screw loose.
Which is why I think you'll survive
a long time in this job. Aki.
Was that an insult?
And I'll eat your almond tofu
if you don't want it.
Just one.
I'm not smoking. It's bad for your bones.
I wish you would. I get the feeling
we're gonna be together for a while.
Just one. then.
This is the first and last
cigarette I ever light up.
Himeno. do you have any smokes left?
Sorry. Last one.
Let me have it. please.
If you insist...
Dude. that's kissing! No fair!
That's an indirect kiss!
Shut up.
I've got bad news.
Remember the devil we killed?
The one that I slew!
Well. he's a lot bigger now.
That really is the one I slew.
It traps us in a hotel...
and its body turns into that?
What the hell kind of devil is this?
Humans. Hear me. humans.
You foolish humans.
I offer you a contract...
It talked!
A contract?
Feed me the human known as Denji.
Even his corpse will do.
Let me eat him.
Do this. and I'll let the rest
of you leave in peace.
You'll be free to leave!
Now. accept this contract!
Do it... Do it...
Denji... let it eat you.
Man. that's obnoxious.
Aki. can't you swallow
this thing with the Fox Devil?
Kon.
Looks like Fox Devil isn't coming.
We're cut off from the rest of the world.
The Fox Devil's body is in Kyoto.
so that makes sense.
Let's see what my Ghost can do. then.
That hurt!
It hurts! Oh. it hurts! The pain!
It hurts...! It hurts!
It got even bigger!
It's pointless!
This isn't my main body...
You won't find my heart here.
You're inside of my stomach...
and I have no weaknesses
on this eighth floor.
There is no way to survive this place.
apart from accepting my offer.
You're probably not gonna
let them go. even if I do die.
Actually. no.
The devil used the word "contract." right?
Those kinds of terms hold a strong sway
when a devil is involved.
If one side makes good on the deal.
the other has to or else.
Whichever side breaks
the contract ends up dying.
So. we would be able to leave
by killing you. Denji.
Himeno... we should kill him.
We can come up with another plan
once he's dead. and we're out of here.
We're all gonna end up starving otherwise.
Devil Hunters are legally allowed to
make contracts with devils.
We should take the deal!
The devil wants Denji dead.
That means his death would benefit it.
which is why we're not accepting.
I'm with him!
But...
I say we kill him!
My Nobel Prize will remain forever out of
reach if I'm unable to leave this place!
You must die for my Nobel.
Fiends can't make pacts with devils.
It wouldn't be obligated to let us leave.
even if you killed him.
Look. we're not killing Denji.
We're Devil Hunters.
We only kill devils.
Shall we wrestle to pass the time. then?
You're just gonna try and kill me! Hell no!
So hungry...
Aki. have you got any kind of plan
for actually getting us out of here?
If what the devil says
is true. we can't kill it.
But we're not killing Denji. either.
So. is the plan to starve. then?
If we really run out of options.
I'll use the sword.
No. you won't.
If that thing can get us out of here.
shouldn't he use it?
He shouldn't use it.
even if we're out of options.
If it comes to that... sorry.
but you'll have to die. Denji!
It's gone?!
It's gone... all the food
that was left on the bed...
None of it's left.
Why?
You ate all of it. didn't you?
'Twas not me. This is Denji's doing.
Of all the obvious lies...
I get it now...
I figured it out.
We can't get out of here because
of that Fiend's power!
That has to be it!
No. it doesn't.
Calm down. Kobeni! This is the Blood Fiend—
So you're taking her side?
Even though we're Devil Hunters?!
You're on the devil's side. Arai!
You're a spy!
He's spycy.
I... I'm not on the devil's side...
I know you're a spy!
Was that a scream?
We need to move!
Kill Denji...
Give me his heart... Give it!
I will grow as your fear grows...
and with your terror. I will capture you!
So. fear me more!
Be overcome by your impending death!
Dread everything.
I will be the one to kill Chainsaw...
It will be me!
The Eternity Devil!
The floor's tilting!
Give me Denji's heart!
Somebody. anybody. kill Denji!
Please make him dead!
We're running out of time!
Let's just feed him to the devil!
I'm using the sword.
You okay with that. Himeno?
Himeno?!
Whoa. lady! What the hell?!
We can probably get out of here
if he uses that sword.
but the pact is one that takes a lot
of years off Aki's life in exchange.
He's got too much to live for.
I'm sorry. Denji.
Damn it!
Hey. get off!
Let me go!
Die!
He might be a piece of shit that
deserves being stabbed a time or two...
But he wants the Gun Devil dead.
And I... can't kill it by myself.
To do that. I need Devil Hunters
with the guts to fight it.
The more. the better...
Even if it costs some of my own life...
I'm not letting Denji die.
Power! You're the Blood Fiend. right?
Can you keep him from bleeding out?
I only have total control over my own blood.
The blood of others is a challenge.
But I suppose I'd need a new
cook if topknot died.
Given that. I have little choice.
What do we do?
What do we do?!
Aki... Aki! Aki. what do we do?!
I-It's not my fault!
You! This is because of you!
If you just let it eat you.
this would all be over!
Yeah. yeah. I get it.
Guess it's snack time. then.
Oh. thank goodness.
I'm not gonna go down smooth. though.
So if I manage to kill this fucking devil...
I still expect to get that kiss!
Have you any plan to win?
It's gonna hurt real bad.
but I'll get my chainsaws out.
Ch-Chainsaws?
I dunno what this devil's deal is.
but it's scared of my chainsaws.
That's why it didn't try to kill me.
and wanted you guys to do it instead.
And I remember it was crying
about pain when it got attacked...
So I figure. if I tear it up until
it can't take the pain no more.
it'll wanna kill itself!
A very devilish idea indeed.
I can't believe you did that for me.
Nobody asked you. Asshole.
I'm through with owing
anybody anything. got it?
So once you're out of here. we're even!